Muhammad Saad FULL-STACK PYTHON

ABOUT ME

A full-stack Python Developer working on projects related to python, Cloud (AWS, GCP). I inspire to become a DevOps Engineer.

Lived in Qatar for 18 years and moved to Pakistan for pursuing Software Engineering at UET TAXILA.

Keen to learn more and implement in life to solve problems using code.

- Python developer (Scripting, Django)
- Data Science (Numpy, Pandas, scikit-learn)
- Firebase Developer
- Actions on Google
- SQL Database Management
- Linux/Unix
- Flutter development

EDUCATION

University of Engineering and technology, Taxila

2018 - 2022 | Bachelor's in Software Engineering

Pakistan International School Qatar

2009 - 2017 | FSc in Pre-engineering

EXPERIENCE

2018-Current

Python Development

- Working on Python projects related to Scripting and back-end
- Django Development for React.js and HTML, CSS, JS front-end.

2019-20

Developer Student Club Core Team Member

- Technical and Non-Technical Lead (GCP and Social Media).
- Conducted workshops related to Machine Learning in Cloud and Actions on Google.

2017 Qatar University Research Intern

- Operated state of the art machinery.
- Worked with the Head of Department of the Research Complex.
- Learned a lot of valuable skills by working along side talented chemical engineers.
- Managed other interns as a senior intern.

CONTACT

+92 309 5688 733 muhdsaad@gmail.com

SKILLS

Python Scripting
Django
Cloud Skills
SQL
Linux
Management

